One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Conflict at the Summit
It's a tsunami!
What power! He truly is a legendary monster!
Aokiji...
Young fool!
H-He stopped it!
Oh, my...
He froze the entire bay!
It's impossible for the ships to move!
Fire!
Destroy the Moby Dick!
Now, let's go!
We've got some solid ground to stand on!
Show them what we can do!
The division commanders have joined the fight! Don't stop attacking!
How nice of them to freeze the ocean!
I was so fired up that it was getting too hot for me!
Guess it won't be that easy...
The vice admirals of Navy HQ are here, too!
I've never seen so many of the vice admirals together in one place!
It's just like a Buster Call!
But when they're up against the Old Man, or us, they're nothing special!
Tsuru-san, stand back!
Don't be ridiculous, youngsters!
Even if I retreated to the ends of the sea, there's no such thing as a safe place anymore.
Ground the ship on the frozen bay!
Take 'em all down!
Our destination is the bay! Advance!
For the Old Man, I'd gladly sacrifice my own life!
Bring it on, Navy HQ!
Let's go, Squard Pirates!
Yeah!
It has finally begun.
What's this? You're gonna fight now?
I merely wish to measure...
to see for myself...
the true distance between us and that man.
That's dangerous!
Run away!
Old Man!
He stopped it... The most powerful slash in the world!
The commander of the Third Division...
Diamond Jozu!
K-Kizaru is here!
Hey, now. That's really bright, you know.
He deflected an admiral's attack?
What?
He's covered in blue flames!
Blue flames?
You can't just...
go straight for...
the King, you know!
You Whitebeard Pirates sure are scary!
What's with his body?
He took Kizaru-san's attack head-on, yet he's still alive!
His ability is as powerful as the rumors said!
A power even more rare than the Logia Fruits...
The Mythical Zoan Type.
Look! His wounds are disappearing!
I don't believe this! How could that attack not work!?
It still hurts.
Liar.
That's the First Division Commander!
No matter what hits him, he recovers by flame...
Marco the Phoenix!
I've never seen a bird like this before...
Hmm... this really hurts.
Liar!
Kizaru-san!
Giant unit! Watch out for attacks coming from the sky, too!
Sure!
The Giants are coming!
Aim for their legs! Bring them down!
You guys, stand back!
Jozu!
What power!
What's he doing?
Try stopping this!
It's a block of ice!
It's way too big!
I swear, those two are just...
They simply went and left their stations!
If we're not here...
who will protect this area?!
That enormous ice-block...
He completely vaporized it!
This is bad!
Volcanic rocks!
We can't let them hit us!
Damn bastard!
One of our ships has been hit!
Get away from the ships!
It's like watching the end of the world!
These flames are too flashy.
Why don't you go light some candles on a birthday cake instead, magma-brat?
You don't like flashy funerals, Whitebeard?
Advance towards the plaza!
Fire! Don't stop!
Don't hesitate!
Advance towards the plaza!
Stop the commanders!
Don't let them reach the shore!
Sink the Moby Dick! Kill Whitebeard!
Here he comes!
Fire!
Break through the blockade of warships!
Ace-kun!
Alright, go!
Little Oars Jr.!
He's the descendant of the Continent-Puller, Oars!
He's enormous! Far larger than an ordinary Giant!
Don't let him into the bay! He's trying to breach our defenses!
So, Oars's descendant is one of Whitebeard's men?
I want him! I want his corpse!
I'm starting to get excited!
Oars!
Ace-kun is a nice guy!
I ain't lettin' ya kill him!